We'll be right back.
The steam whistle forces friends apart.
The C-Train starts to run.
All right, I'll give you one last chance.
I'll call off my mid-fernell, but once we're on that train, they're gonna tear you limb from limb.
Listen, jerks.
If I were you, I'd quit while I was in...
Oh, come on.
Why is he here?
Excellent work as always, sirs and madam.
Here, Mr. Lutia, Colt.
What is this, a parade?
Stop it.
It's foolish.
Ah, right.
Sorry, sir.
This isn't over until we reach Eni's lobby, so look sharp.
Everyone board the C-Train immediately.
You heard the man.
Get on the train and make it quick.
Hey, you bastard's gonna put me down or...
Who are those guys in the suits?
He says he's sorry for causing us so much trouble.
Then he goes and gets in trouble all over again.
A little further to the right!
Spray over there!
Bring the hose this way!
We've almost got it!
I think we're good over here for now.
Go see if you can help out with the injure.
Right!
I'm on it!
Is there anyone left inside?
Hey!
Watch your step over there!
So, you mean Robin?
Robin doesn't hate us after all?
Uh-huh!
I'm so happy!
Huh?
He's a raccoon dog?
I thought he was a reindeer.
Did he just transform or what?
Anyway, Chopper, we have to find the rest of the crew right away so we can go rescue Robin.
Okay, let's go!
Uh, but where are they?
I don't know.
That's why we have to find them.
Yeah!
Let's do this!
Whoa!
Now he's a gorilla!
Wait, you two.
Huh?
I don't care if you go after Nico Robin, but before you run off, you should know that the C-Train for government personnel is departing at 11 o'clock tonight.
This is just my guess, but there's a good chance you'll find CP-9 there.
And that means Nico Robin will be there as well.
Thanks to Aqua Laguna, they're stopping all service after this final departure.
In other words, you won't be able to chase him on another train.
Wait, you mean we have to...
Hmm.
Since you obviously can't sail in this weather, you won't be able to leave the island unless you go after that train right now.
Huh?
No way!
What time is it?
Almost 10.30.
What?
That means we've only got half an hour left!
Hey, but you're the mayor, right?
Can't you do something to stop the train?
Well, unfortunately, it's bound for Eni's lobby, which is only accessible to government personnel.
Even the engine driver works for the government, so I have no say in this matter.
Oh, no.
I guess our only choice is to head to the station and try to talk some sense into Robin.
Chopper?
Huh?
I'll tell you which direction Luffy and Zoro flew off in, so you go search there, okay?
If you find them, tell them to come to the station as quickly as they can.
Okay, got it!
Hey, listen up!
Oh, look, you guys!
Polly's okay!
See that girl over there?
I want you to help her find her buddies.
You sure that smoke didn't get in your brain, Polly?
These are the guys that tried to kill Mr. Iceberg!
We should ring their no-good sorry necks!
Besides, why should we waste our time helping some criminals when Luchi and Kaku are still missing?
The Straw Hats aren't the ones who did it, okay?
The real criminals set them up!
We hadn't been so damn blind.
We wouldn't be in this situation right now.
I don't know the real identity of those guys in the masks, but I do know that the Straw Hats tried to protect us from them.
As a matter of fact, Iceberg and I wouldn't even be alive right now if it wasn't for their help.
Don't bother looking for Luchi and Kaku.
There's no point.
In fact, I don't know if we'll ever be seeing them again.
What? If you know what happened to the foreman, then you gotta tell us, Polly.
They went back home.
Huh? Why would they do that at a time like this?
Just shut up and go find Straw Hat.
Hey, immoral girl.
What? You're still calling me that?
If you're going to the station, I'll show you the way.
Uh, thanks, I guess.
Hey, hold on a sec, Polly. Is that stuff you told us true?
Quit your yapping and help them out already! You're making Galilaw look bad!
Yes! Sorry, sir!
We'll do our best!
You're the boss!
Yeah! We'll help any way we can!
Open the cage! Bring out the Yagadas!
Yeah!
Went back home, did they?
I spared them the details. It's better that way.
It was bad enough when we found out they deserved the truth, but I don't want to hurt those guys.
Hey, Chopper, it's all up to you now!
Right! All my Lupian Zorro, you can count on me!
You can count on me!
Hey, guys, can you hear me?
Luffy!
Zorro!
Sanji!
Usap, you can come with us too, okay?
Now shed it with me!
All right, buddy, you got it! Let's do it, guys!
Hey! Luffy!
Zorro!
Sanji!
Usap, you can come with us too!
Take that canal over on the left-hand side! It's a shortcut to the station!
We still have 20 minutes before the train leaves.
Don't go, Robin.
You don't have to sacrifice yourself.
We can save you!
Mr. Yagada, you think you can go a little bit faster, please?
Move, move, move!
The 11 o'clock train is about to depart.
All passengers going from Blue Station to Emmy's Lobby.
Please board immediately.
That hurts!
I don't want to hear another word out of you two.
Well, maybe I wouldn't complain so much if you weren't such big jerkwads!
Yeah, you big jerkwads!
Why don't you come over here and fight?
Hey, that's too much!
Due to the approaching storm surge,
the departure time has been moved up
and the train will be departing shortly.
Damn it.
This was bad enough already.
After all these years,
our mission has finally come to an end.
We're not there yet.
Stop spouting nonsense
and take your mission seriously, you fool.
My apologies.
You can't sail in this weather.
Unless you can catch that train,
you won't be able to leave.
Come on!
We're so close!
Woo!
Frankie,
wherever you are,
I hope you're safe.
Hey, Lupe!
Row, row, go away!
Lupe!
Hey!
Come back!
Who are you?
Come on, there's not much time!
Zoro! Sanji!
Musa, you can come too.
Luffy! Please, those guys are gonna take Robin away!
We need your help! Where are you?
I wonder how the rest of the crew is dealing with this mess.
Anyway, time's up. They'll have to catch me later.
I repeat, the final train will be departing ahead of schedule.
Please board immediately.
You bastards!
I'm coming for you! Just wait, you'll see!
Once I get out of here!
My little slip-up, then this crap happens!
I'm coming for you bastards!
Once I get out of here!
Help me! Zoro! Sanji!
Where are you?
We gotta save Robin!
Zoro!
Roronewa!
I don't get it. Where in the heck are they?
Have we checked over there yet?
Hey!
Roronewa!
Zoro!
I guess they're not here.
Has anybody checked over in the back streets yet?
I don't know if we can.
They're probably completely flooded by now.
It'd be too dangerous to look for them there.
Come on, guys!
Where are you?
There's no time!
Time!
Excuse me!
The waves are getting dangerously high, so we've decided to depart early as a safety measure.
If there's any trouble, we could...
It's fine. Just go.
Just go.
夢見た僕らは間違いじゃないと信じて 荒く埋める海原を渡って行ける
誰よりも勇敢で思いやりもあるけれど
もしも君がこの船を降りて 違う世界にいたとしても
最後にはきっと笑えるよ
誰かを サンジー乗ろう人と思ったら
どうも 大丈夫を変 θにする
Sanji barges in!
C-Train battle in the storm!
I'm gonna be king of the pirates!